suddenvalues.com 2007-01-28

# 

US Online.com, Inc., a Washington corporation ("US Online") maintains this web site as a service to its customers. By using web sites owned and operated by US Online or its affiliates, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms of use, which may change at any time. 

**Information Collection**  
US Online collects information from our users at several different points on our website, and is the sole owner of the information collected. 

**Registration**  
In order to use certain features of this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. Also the form requests the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as social security number), so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. 

**Orders**  
We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used primarily for billing purposes and to fill customer`s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user`s hard drive containing information about the user. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able customize the feel and content on our website. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user`s movement at an aggregated level, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**  
We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information you give US ONLINE for any secondary purposes. We partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that US Online shall not be responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, US Online, may ask for contact information such as name and email address. 

**Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Tell-A-Friend**  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend`s name and email address. US Online will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. US Online stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact US Online at [support@corp.usonline.com](mailto:support@corp.usonline.com) to request the removal of this information from our database. 

**Security**  

When US Online`s registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just `surfing`. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, US Online shall not be responsible for any economic damage incurred by the provider of such sensitive information in the event that such sensitive information is obtained by a third party. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [support@corp.usonline.com](mailto:support@corp.usonline.com). 

**Special Offers**  
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below. 

**Site and Service Updates**  
We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:**  
If a user`s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user`s personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support. [Some sites may also provide telephone or postal mail options for updating or correcting personal information]. 

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to `opt-out` of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, an order form might have an `opt-out` mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don`t want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or email us at [support@corp.usonline.com](mailto:support@corp.usonline.com). US Online, attempts to notify users of our site when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not.
